<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on IBS Government Services</title>
    <link>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on IBS Government Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Audit Remediation Services</title>
      <link>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/services/remediation-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/services/remediation-services/</guid>
      <description>We provide audit support, readiness, and remediation, as well as liaison assistance with external stakeholders such as the Office of Inspector General (OIG), Government Accountability Office (GAO), and independent public accountants (IPAs).
CFO Act audit support, readiness, and remediation IT audit and technology risk support Technical consultation on accounting matters in accordance with FASAB, FAM, FFMIA, FMFIA, GAGAS, OMB, and GAO regulations</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Management Services</title>
      <link>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/services/financial-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/services/financial-management/</guid>
      <description>We provide a wide array of financial management services to our Federal Government clients such as accounting budgeting, and financial reporting support.
 Budget Formulation and Execution Acquisition Management Financial Program Management Accounting Operations and Services  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Sung</title>
      <link>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/team/anthony-sung/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/team/anthony-sung/</guid>
      <description>Mr. Sung has more than 20 years of accounting and government auditing experience including financial, compliance, internal controls, information technology, and property management services in the Federal Government arena. Mr. Sung is responsible for maintaining and developing the firm&amp;rsquo;s internal organization processes and infrastructure, as well as coordinating the delivery of client services. Mr. Sung is responsible for all aspects of IBS Government Services day-to-day operations and administration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agency Compliance Support</title>
      <link>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/services/compliance-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/services/compliance-support/</guid>
      <description>We provide expertise and hands-on support to help agencies achieve compliance with limited budgets. Our process improvement, risk management, and regulations experts work with clients to improve the processes and controls needed to achieve compliance in the most efficient manner possible.
 OMB A-123 Appendix A, B, C Federal Financial Management Improvement Act (FFMIA) Federal Managers Financial Integrity Act (FMFIA) Federal Information Security Management Act (FISMA)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accountant</title>
      <link>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/careers/accountant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:05:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/careers/accountant/</guid>
      <description> Accountant 
Responsibilities
 Preparing, examining and analyzing accounting records, financial statements, and other financial reports to assess accuracy and conformance to reporting and procedural standards Providing internal and external auditing support services for government agencies Maintaining and examining government agencies&amp;rsquo; records Creating budgets and consolidated financial statements by analyzing business operations, trends, costs, revenues, financial commitments, audits and obligations  
Requirements
 Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Accounting, Finance or related field CPA, CISA, CGFM, and CDFM preferred Understanding USSGL Strong understanding of OMB Circular A-123 and A-136 TS/SCI with Poly  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federal Budget Analyst</title>
      <link>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/careers/federal-budget-analyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:05:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/careers/federal-budget-analyst/</guid>
      <description> Federal Budget Analyst 
Responsibilities
 Analyzing monthly department budgeting and accounting reports to maintain expenditure controls and ensure completeness, accuracy, and conformance with procedures and regulations Directing the preparation of regular and special budget reports Providing advice and technical assistance with cost analysis, fiscal allocation, and budget preparation Performing cost-benefits analyses to compare operating programs, review financial requests, and explore alternative financing methods  
Requirements
 Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Accounting, Finance or related field CPA, CISA, CGFM, and CDFM preferred Experience with budget analysis, planning, and programming and the relative financial systems in national security government agencies TS/SCI with Poly  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Financial Analyst</title>
      <link>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/careers/senior-financial-analyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:05:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyle-sung.github.io/ibs-govt-services/careers/senior-financial-analyst/</guid>
      <description> Senior Financial Analyst 
Responsibilities
 Guiding cost analysis processes by establishing and enforcing policies and procedures, providing trends and forecasts, explaining processes and techniques and recommending actions Reviewing financial statuses and establishing budgets Identifying financial risk, reviewing and evaluation financial reports and accounting transactions processes including controls related to federal entities  
Requirements
 Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in accounting, finance or business; CPA or other certifications preferred Federal audit consulting/accounting experience in business process improvement, financial management policies and procedures, budget formulation and execution, and financial system integrations Experience within the Intelligence Community or Department of Defense a plus TS/SCI with Poly  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>